sploder.com 2018-10-31

# Privacy Policy - Make your own Games Online for Free

### Privacy Policy

This is the Sploder™ privacy policy. If you have questions about this policy, or about the information stored in your account, we can be reached via e-mail via our contact form.

#### Types of Information Collected

For each visitor to our site, our web server automatically recognizes the visitor's referrer and IP address for authentication and security purposes.

Registrants under the age of 13 are not permitted to submit any personal information on [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/). This includes e-mail addresses. Those under the age of 13 may provide the e-mail address of a legal parent or guardian. E-mail addresses are not saved or stored in the system. They are only used to generate an access key for password retrieval.

This site does not collect age-related information from users.

Please note that the forums at [forums.sploder.com](http://forums.sploder.com/) are an optional feature of [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/). They require a separate registration and are **age-restricted**. The forum software at [forums.sploder.com](http://forums.sploder.com/) will collect e-mail addresses in order for authentication, password resetting, approvals and forum-related system notices. Members who join [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/) are **not** automatically registered on [forums.sploder.com](http://forums.sploder.com/), and they must be 13 or older to register there.

Third party ad networks and analytics providers may collect certain types of information about your visit, including whether you interacted with content. No personally identifiable information will be collected.

#### How the Information is Used

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor. **Account information is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.**

Clients can change most account information online. Information that cannot be changed online can be corrected by sending us a message via our contact form.

#### Cookies

The system uses cookies to record session information, so that the client's data files and content remain accessible accross multiple page-views in the site.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on visits to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display the advertisements and links that appear on [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/) which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [sploder.com](http://www.sploder.com/)'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

#### E-mail Communication

This site does not engage in e-mail based marketing. E-mails are sent to users only when an e-mail authentication is required, or when a user initiates a support request via the contact form. Any user under the age of 13 must communicate through a parent.

Registered users may also choose to disallow all user-to-user communication in their account settings.

#### Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving client data exchanged with our site.

#### Deleting your account.

Registered users may permanently delete their account and account data at any time from the account management interface.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via our contact form.
